{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-3",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 3",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "english-5",
    "unit3",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 3: My foreign friends",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "foreign",
      "answer": "nước ngoài",
      "speak": "foreign"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "nationality",
      "answer": "quốc tịch",
      "speak": "nationality"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Australian",
      "answer": "người Úc",
      "speak": "australian"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Malaysian",
      "answer": "người Malaysia",
      "speak": "malaysian"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "American",
      "answer": "người Mỹ",
      "speak": "american"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Japanese",
      "answer": "người Nhật",
      "speak": "japanese"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "British",
      "answer": "người Anh",
      "speak": "british"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Indian",
      "answer": "người Ấn Độ",
      "speak": "indian"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Chinese",
      "answer": "người Trung Quốc",
      "speak": "chinese"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "friendly",
      "answer": "thân thiện",
      "speak": "friendly"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "helpful",
      "answer": "hữu ích, sẵn sàng giúp đỡ",
      "speak": "helpful"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "clever",
      "answer": "thông minh",
      "speak": "clever"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "active",
      "answer": "năng động",
      "speak": "active"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "classmate",
      "answer": "bạn cùng lớp",
      "speak": "classmate"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "age",
      "answer": "tuổi tác",
      "speak": "age"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "appearance",
      "answer": "ngoại hình",
      "speak": "appearance"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "personality",
      "answer": "tính cách",
      "speak": "personality"
    }
  ]
}